Guide to the Wanda Gifford Photographs 1948-1958
Oregon State University Libraries, University Archives
- Numbered Photographs, 1948-1957; Series I; 1946 negatives and 884 prints
  - Bicycle girl; Rundle Mountain reflection, Canada, 0784
    - 4x5 negative (Box 11)
    - 5 prints (Box 5, 76)
  - Art Silander; Mt. Temple, 0785; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Wapta Lake, 0786; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Moraine Lake, 0787; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Bridge at Kicking Horse Canyon, 0788; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - A mountain valley, 0789; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - The Great Divide between British Columbia and Alberta; Alberta side, 0790; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - The Great Divide between British Columbia and Alberta; British Columbia side, 0791; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Logan Pass, Glacier National Park, Montana, 0792; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Strawberry pickers, 0793; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 11)
  - Two young boys picking strawberries, 0794; 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 67)
  - Strawberry pickers turning in filled carriers, 0795-0796; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Man standing in strawberry field, 0797; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Strawberry pickers, 0798; 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 67)
  - Farmhouse, 0799; 6 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Tractor plowing field, 0800; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Tractor plowing field, 0801; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Dr. Simmons, Silverton, Oregon, pouring grain into seeder, 0802; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Dr. Simmons at work with his tractor and seeder, 0803-0804; 3 print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 11)
  - Tractor and seeder? at work, 0805-0806; 3 prints and 2 4x5 diacetate negatives (Box 5, 67)
  - Tractor plowing fields, 0807; print and 4x5 diacetate negatives (Box 5, 67)
  - Tractor plowing fields, 0808; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Mr. Seins, Silverton, Oregon, on his John Deere tractor plowing pasture sod, 0809; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Tractor plowing fields, 0810; 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 67)
  - Tractor plowing fields, 0811; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Tractor at work, 0812; 3 prints and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - H.A. Barnes farm; dairy cows in pasture, 0813; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Strawberry pickers, 0814-0816
    - 0814, 4x5 negative (Box 11)
    - 0815-0816, 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 11)
  - Kaffun Family portraits, 0817; 12 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Photos of a girl and toddler (Gifford Family?), 0818; 6 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Dairy cows, Parkdale; Hood in background, 0819; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Dairy cows, Parkdale; Hood in background, 0820; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Tractor tilling ground, 0821; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Pickers in orchard, 0822; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Walter Maurer, Parkdale, Oregon, hauling in Newton Apples on his 30-acre farm with a Ford tractor, 0823; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Apple pickers, Hood River, Oregon, 0824; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Apple filled branches, Hood River, Oregon, 0825; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Branches weighed down by apples, 0826; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Loading trailer with apples, 0827; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
    Possibly same farm as image 0823.
  - Loading trailer with apples, 0828; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Loading Newton apples on Walter Maurer's 30-acre farm, Parkdale, Oregon, 0829; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Apple pickers, 0830; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Jerry Routson of Parkdale, Oregon in the Hood River Valley busily picks his fine crop of D'Anjou pears. He had a large crew of men working in various parts of the orchard. Full boxes of pears were scattered all through the orchard awaiting hauling to the packing sheds, 0831; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Unloading Newton apples under walnut tree on Walter Maurer's 30 acre orchard, Parkdale, Oregon, 0832; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Pear picker, 0833; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Apple orchard, 0834; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Pictures of a girl and baby, 0835; 11 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Grain elevator with a pile of wheat beside it, Ritzville, Washington, 0836; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Walnut orchard being pruned for winter kill and long neglect; rather severe pruning in parts of orchard, 0837; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Spraying peach and walnut orchards with the help of a tractor, 0838-841; prints for 838 & 839 and 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 11)
    - 0838-839, 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 11)
    - 0840-841, 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Orchard from a distance, 0842-0844; 4 print and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 11)
  - Spraying peach and walnut orchards with the help of a tractor, 0845; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Training boysenberries, 0847-0848; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Securing wire on hop job; tractor pulling high tower, 0849; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Migrant houses, Dayton farm labor camp, 0850; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Boys on fence at Dayton farm labor camp, 0851; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - "One of the better houses at the Dayton Camp. I found people living all winter in this house. However they were not working. Men about the grounds said they did not have jobs", 0852; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Dayton farm labor camp, 0853; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mr. Glen Lucas cultivating improved Santiam blackberries, Gervais, Oregon; data: plow tractor model manufactured by Simplicity Company for Montgomery Ward, 3 hp engine, 0854; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Interior of migrant camp house, Salem, Oregon; "Showing one of the units of the camp at Salem, Oregon. Water is to be found outside. There is a central shower room and lavatories, also laundry room and a large club room at this camp", 0855; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Exterior of a migrant camp house, Salem, Oregon, 0856; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - "A part of the housing camp for migratory workers on the berry farm of Mr. Gildwell, North Santiam, Oregon. Some tent houses are used. Water electric lights and wood are furnished;" long shot, 0857; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - "Group of houses used as a camp for workers on the farm of Mr. Gildwell, North Santiam, Oregon. There are more that are not shown in the picture. Mr. Gildwell housed about 20 families during the summer or harvest season", 0858; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - U.S. dredge Luckiamute on the Willamette River, 0859; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Geese in strawberry field, 0860; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - City street next to Willamette River, 0861; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Champion bulls, polled hereford sale; Joe Johnson, Domino, Hibberd, Ray Robinson, March 15, 1951; 0862; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Champion bulls; hereford sale, 0863-0864; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Roy C. Meyer loading milk truck on Walter Drager dairy farm, Gervais, Oregon, 0865; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Dairy tour viewing alta fescue pasture grass, Walter Drager farm, 0866; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Ben Newell, Marion County agent; Newton Davis; LaMarr; at Newton Davis farm dairy tour, 0867; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Jersey herd on pasture, 0868; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Ground silo, Walter Drager farm, Gervais, Oregon, 0869; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Jersey herd on spring pasture, 0870; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Hood, Hood River, 0918; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Hood apple blossoms, 0919; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Mt. Adams plum? blooms, May 5, 1953; 0920; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Adams with apple trees in foreground; taken in Proctor orchard, Hood River Valley, Oregon, 0921; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Mt. Adams and Hood River Valley, 0922; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Apple orchard; John Hancock, Salem, Oregon, 0923; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Apple blooms; John Hancock, Salem, Oregon, 0924; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Adams and Hood River Valley, May 5, 1951; 0925; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
    Good print.
  - Apple orchard; John Hancock, 0926; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Apple bloom; John Hancock (good close up), 0927; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Apple blossoms, 0928; 3 prints and 3 120 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Apple blossoms; close up, 0929; print and 2 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Strawberry field; John Hancock, 0930; 4x5 negative and 120 negative (Box 11)
  - Strawberry blooms close up, 0931-0933
    - 0931-0932, 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
    - 0933, print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Strawberry blooms close up (Rolli), 0934-0935; 2 prints and 2 120 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Mr. T. Brewster spraying boysenberries, 0936-0939; prints for 936, 938, & 939 and 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
    - 0936, print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
    - 0937, 4x5 negative (Box 11)
    - 0938-0939, 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Church spires, Salem, 0958; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Post office, Salem, Oregon, 0959; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Marion County Courthouse interior views, 0960; print and 5 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Swift Current Falls, Glacier National Park, 0961; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Swift Current Falls and Grinnel Peak, Glacier National Park (Box 6)
    Similar to image 0961.
  - Bridge over small river on the coast, 0962; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Fossil Beds, John Day (close up), 0963; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Fossil Beds, group Chemeketans? digging, 0964; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Sheep Mountain Fossil Beds, John Day River, 0965-0966; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Cathedral Spires, John Day River in foreground, 0967; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Fossil Beds, John Day, 0968; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Group gathered on car lined road, Fossil Beds, 0969; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Cathedral Spires from John Day highway, 0970; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Bridge over John Day River in Fossil Bed Park, 0971; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Cathedral Spires, 0972; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Fossil Bed Park, car on highway, 0973; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Cattle pen, 0974; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - River, 0975; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
    3 paper; 10 to 12 counts
  - Cattle in a field, 0976; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Barn with the Three Sisters? in the background, 0977; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mountain framed by trees, 0978; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Sightseers atop mountain, 0979; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Mountain climbers standing on a mountainside, 0980; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Valley with a mountain in background, 0981; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - The Three Sisters?, 0982; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - View of Prineville? from a hillside, 0983; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Crooked River Gorge and Bridge, 0984; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
    Ben negative; image taken by Ben L. Gifford (?).
  - Armeo railing on edge of Ochoco Dam taken Memorial Day, 0985; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Small mountain from road, 0986; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Headwaters of the Metolius River; Mt. Jefferson in background, 0987; oversize print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11, 76)
  - Mt. Jefferson?, 0988; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - The Three Sisters from Scott Lake, boy on raft (evening shot), 0989; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - The Three Sisters, 0990; oversize print and 4x5 negative (Box 11, 76)
  - Mt. Jefferson, Oregon; headwaters of Metolius River, 0991; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Mt. Washington? and Blue Lake?, 0992; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Two of the Three Sisters, 0993; oversize print and 4x5 negative (Box 11, 76)
  - Woman gazing at field with Three Sisters? in the background, 0994; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Washington? with Blue Lake? in foreground, 0995; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Headwaters of the Metolius River; Mt. Jefferson in the background, 0996; oversize print and 4x5 negative (Box 11, 76)
  - The Three Sisters from Scott Lake, 0997-0998
    - 0997, 4x5 negative and oversize print (Box 11, 74)
    - 0998, 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Shuksan; scenic reflection, Summer 1951; 0999
    - 4x5 negative (Box 11)
    - 5 prints (Box 6, 76)
  - Mt. Shuksan and Leah, Summer 1951; 1000; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Mt. Shuksan, Summer 1951; 1001; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Three women viewing Mt. Shuksan, Summer 1951; 1002; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Mt. Baker, Summer 1951; 1003; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
    Telephoto.
  - Mt. Baker, Summer 1951; 1004; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
    Vertical view.
  - Mt. Baker at bridge, Summer 1951; 1005; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Mt. Baker and Baker Lake?, Summer 1951; 1006-1007
    - 1006, 4x5 negative (Box 11)
    - 1007, print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Leah and Bessie at camp near Mt. Baker, Summer 1951; 1008; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Mt. Baker and Baker Lake?, Summer 1951; 1009; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Chemeketa Group in boat?, 1010; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Group of women hikers at spring, 1011; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Group of women hikers at spring, 1012; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Mt. Baker, Summer 1951; 1013; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - People at camp, 1014; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - River Canyon, 1015; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Incline railway up a steep cliff, 1016; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Baker, Summer 1951; 1017; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Woman viewing mountians (Mt. Baker?), 1018; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Large mountian (Mt. Shuksan?) with lake in foreground, 1019; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Snow capped mountians in a oak tree frame, 1020; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Baker from highway bridge, Summer 1951; 1021; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Baker, Summer 1951; 1022; print and 10 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
    Includes view (1022-J) of a dam under construction.
  - Irrigation canal; mountain in background, 1023; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Young orchard with a mountain in the background, 1024; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Orchard with a mountain in the background, 1025; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Orchard with a mountain in the background, 1026; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Orchard with a mountain in the background, 1027; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Blooming orchards in Hood River Valley with Mt. Adams in the background, 1028; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
    Touring by car through the beautiful Hood River Valley in spring with the orchards in bloom; Mt. Adams in background.
  - Orchard with a mountain in the background, 1029; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Young orchard, 1030; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Judge Joe Fulton, 1031; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Judge Rex Kimell, 1032; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Judge Duncan, 1033; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
    6 overall F8 burn in table and foreground 2
  - George R. Duncan, May 1953; 1034; 4 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Willamette University, Oregon, 1035; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Public Service Building, 1036; 2 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Post Office from Courthouse, 1037; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Willamette University, 1038; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Sunset over the Willamette River, 1039a-1039b; oversize print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11, 76)
  - Cove on coast with waterfalls, 1040; 3 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Men lifting glass off truck to put in Stan Baker Motors window, 1041-1042; 5 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Men putting glass in Stan Baker Motors window, 1043; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Men putting glass in Stan Baker Motors window; finishing touches, 1044; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Swift Current Falls, Glacier National Park, 1048; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mountain lake, 1049; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Campsite, 1050; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mountain lake, 1051; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Swift Current Falls, Glacier National Park, 1052; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Lake, 1053; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Swift Current Falls, Glacier National Park, 1054; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Steep canyon, 1055; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Lake, 1056; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Flat of strawberries, 1057; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Girl picking strawberries, 1058; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - O.G. Frogley strawberry field, near Salem, Oregon, 1059; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Onion field, 1060; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Strawberries, 1061-1062; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Strawberry pickers, 1063; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Flat of strawberries, close up, 1064; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Close up of unpicked strawberries, 1065; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Loading flats of strawberries into truck, 1066; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Farmer hand dusting his field, 1067; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Onion field, 1068; 4 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Close up of strawberries on the bush, 1069; 120 negative (Box 11)
  - Dusting pesticides? on fields with tractor; refilling dust tanks, 4x5 negative; 1070 (Box 11)
  - Farmer dusting strawberries with a tractor, 1071; 120 negative (Box 11)
  - Strawberry pickers, 1072; 120 negative (Box 11)
  - Young girl picking strawberries, 1073-1074; 2 120 negatives (Box 11)
  - Farmer dusting strawberries with a tractor, 1076; 120 negative (Box 11)
  - Farmer dusting strawberries (Box 6)
    Similar to image 1076.
  - Strawberry field, 1077; 120 negative (Box 11)
  - Strawberry pickers; Ramey patch, Salem, Oregon, 1080; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Pop Kin A Wane, 2 4x5 copy negatives; 1081 (Box 11)
    Copy negatives of photograph taken by Benjamin A. Gifford.
  - Hash-Nash-Shut, Indian man, 1082; 4x5 copy negative (Box 11)
    Copy negative of photograph taken by Benjamin A. Gifford.
  - Close up of strawberries, 1083-1084; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - From corner of Hearts Delight, 1085; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Hearts Delight, Mary Kueny home, Steens Mountain, 1086; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Steens Mountian as seen from Alvord Ranch (Rolli shot taken from yard; pretty shot), 1087; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Hearts Delight, Kueny home on Wild Horse Creek; entrance; home in background; Steens Mountain, 1088; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Home ranch Kueny place looking north; irrigation ditch in foreground; tall pasture; bunk house; machinery shed, 1089; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Wild Horse Creek; Hearts Delight in background; shown relative to mountains, 1093; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Thru gate looking south Penblo Range; home ranch Kueny, 1094; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Taken from Kueny home ranch; Steens Mountain, 1095; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Road between fields and Andrews; Steens Mountain, 1096; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mary Kueny; V. Lake; high in Steens Mountain, 1097; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - V. Lake; Steens Mountain, 1098; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - "Mornin' on the Desert" poem and views of a high desert valley, 1099; 1 print and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
    Mary Kueny negative.
  - John Divine Rock, Steens Mountain, 1100; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Steen Mountains from Alvord? Ranch, 1101; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Sunset, Oregon coast, 1103; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - River meeting ocean, 1104; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
    Cloud negative used with this.
  - High seas, Oregon coast, 1105; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Breakers, Oregon coast, 1106; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - High breakers, Oregon coast, 1107; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Yaquina Bay Bridge at Newport, Oregon, 1108 (Box 6)
  - Sheep and lambs, 1109; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Sheep and lambs, 1110; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Boone's Ferry, Willamette River, 1111; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Railroad bridge and highway overpass over a road, 1112; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Highway overpass, 1113; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Drainage culvert under road, 1114; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Highway overpass; Interstate 5 construction?, 1115; 4 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Construction of Interstate 5 from a highway overpass, 1116; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Drainage ditch, 1117; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Ferry landing; highway bridge over river in background, 1118; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Wayside park on Blue Star Memorial Highway, 1119; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - House from front, 1120; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - House from side, 1121; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - House from corner, 1122; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - House from front, 1123; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - House from side, 1124; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Pigs at creek side, 1125; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Pigs, 1126; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - 2 women standing next to a man playing an accordion, 1127; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Boys playing pool and table tennis, 1128; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - A group photo, 1129; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - House from side, 1130; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Highway overpass, 1131; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - House from corner, 1132-1133; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Clouds, 1134; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Covered bridge, 1135; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Covered bridge, 1136; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
    7 counts 10 m foreground 20 for sky
  - Covered bridge, 1137; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
    7 counts; 2 paper
  - Covered bridge, 1138; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Covered bridge, 1139; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Stream, 1140; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Pleasant Grove Church, 1141-1142; 4 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Close up of turkeys, 1143; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Turkeys, 1144-1145; 5 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Mt. McLaughlin and Lake of Woods, 1146-1147; 2 print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 6, 11)
  - Four Mile Lake with Mt. McLaughlin in the background, May 30, 1954; 1148; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
    The photographer was standing on the edge of the dam near the head gates of the flume when this picture was taken; the lake is well stocked with trout and is a mecca for Southern Oregon fishermen. 1/25 at F22; K2 filter.
  - Mt. McLaughlin and Lake of Woods, May 30, 1954; 1149; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
  - Irrigation flume, 1150; print and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
    Upper view of irrigation flume showing where Armco pipe has been used around a hill side to maintain the proper water level for the flume; this irrigation ditch or flume is high in the Cascade range, heading in Four Mile Lake from where the water is conveyed down to the Medford Valley, Oregon for irrigation purposes.
  - Irrigation flume, 1151; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 6, 11)
    This stretch of flume made with Armco pipe is a link in a long irrigation ditch which heads in 4 Mile Lake high in the Cascade Mountains and runs down into the Valley around Medford, Oregon for irrigation purposes. Part of the flume is formed along the hill sides by excavating the dirt and using the earth from the ditch for a very narrow road to travel in the maintenance of this long flume. Hundreds of fishermen also travel this dike formed road to reach 4 Mile Lake which is amply stocked with trout.
  - Interior views of Methodist Church, Salem, Oregon, 1152; 11 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
    Includes images of worship services and classes.
  - Old bridge new pier, 1153; 120 negative (Box 11)